Doll & Richards Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Financial Records, 1871-1973, bulk 1902-1969, Series 5:; (Boxes 18-69, 79, BV81-112; 55 linear feet)
  - Sales Records, circa 1883, 1901-1973, bulk 1902-1968, 5.2:
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 31)
      - Nos. 47,400-47,499, October 1-31, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Nos. 47,500-47,599, November 1 - December 13, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Nos. 47,600-47,699, December 13, 1904 - January 30, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Nos. 47,700-47,799, January 31 - June 15, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Nos. 47,800-47,899, June 15 - October 18, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Nos. 47,900-47,999, October 19 - December 19, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Nos. 48,000-48,099, December 20, 1905 - March 5, 1906 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Nos. 48,100-48,199, March 5 - May 23, 1906 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Nos. 48,200-48,299, May 23 - August 28, 1906 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Nos. 48,300-48,399, August 28 - November 14, 1906 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Nos. 48,400-48,499, November 14, 1906 - January 22, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Nos. 48,500-48,599, January 23 - April 11, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Nos. 48,600-48,699, April 11 - December 11, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Nos. 48,700-48,799, December 17, 1907 - January 27, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 32)
      - Nos. 48,800-48,899, January 29 - October 21, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Nos. 48,900-48,999, October 21 - December 6, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Nos. 49,000-49,099, December 6, 1909 - January 11, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Nos. 49,100-49,199, January 11 - March 2, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Nos. 49,200-49,299, March 2 - April 18, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Nos. 49,300-49,399, April 20 - September 23, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Nos. 49,400-49,499, September 23, 1910 - February 1, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Nos. 49,500-49,599, February 1 - June 14, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Nos. 49,600-49,699, June 14 - October 14, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Nos. 49,700-49,799, October 16, 1911 - January 1, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Nos. 49,800-49,899, January 3 - July 24, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Nos. 49,900-49,999, July 24, 1912 - July 7, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Nos. 50,000-50,099, July 16, 1913 - July 15, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Nos. 50,100-50,199, August 6, 1914 - August 20, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Nos. 50,200-50,299, August 21, 1915 - January 30, 1917 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Nos. 50,300-50,399, February 8, 1917 - April 3, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Nos. 50,400-50,499, April 6, 1918 - March 24, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Nos. 50,500-50,599, April 1, 1920 - May 20, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Nos. 50,600-50,699, May 31, 1922 - October 13, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Nos. 50,700-50,799, October 18, 1923 - January 4, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Nos. 50,800-50,899, January 4 - March 10, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Nos. 50,900-50,999, March 10 - May 23, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Nos. 51,000-51,099, May 26 - September 26, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Nos. 51,100-51,199, September 29 - December 2, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Nos. 51,200-51,299, December 1, 1924 - January 30, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Nos. 51,300-51,399, January 30 - April 28, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 33)
      - Nos. 51,400-51,499, May 1 - August 25, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Nos. 51,500-51,599, August 26 - October 21, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Nos. 51,600-51,699, October 21 - December 2, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Nos. 51,700-51,799, December 2, 1925 - January 16, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Nos. 51,800-51,899, December 30, 1925 - May 3, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Nos. 51,900-51,999, May 5 - October 18, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Nos. 52,000-52,099, October 18 - November 27, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Nos. 52,100-52,199, November 27, 1926 - January 11, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Nos. 52,200-52,299, January 11 - March 4, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Nos. 52,300-52,399, March 4 - April 4, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Nos. 52,400-52,499, April 4 - June 21, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Nos. 52,500-52,599, June 22 - September 28, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Nos. 52,600-52,699, September 29 - November 21, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Nos. 52,700-52,799, November 22 - December 14, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Nos. 52,800-52,899, December 14, 1927 - January 13, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Nos. 52,900-52,999, January 14 - March 16, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Nos. 53,000-53,099, March 17 - June 6, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Nos. 53,100-53,199, June 6 - August 24, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Nos. 53,200-53,299, August 24 - September 22, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Nos. 53,300-53,399, September 24 - October 18, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Nos. 53,400-53,499, October 19 - November 8, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Nos. 53,500-53,599, November 9 - December 4, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Nos. 53,600-53,699, December 4-20, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Nos. 53,700-53,799, December 21, 1928 - January 21, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Nos. 53,800-53,899, January 21 - February 25, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Nos. 53,900-53,999, February 25 - March 25, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 34)
      - Nos. 54,000-54,099, March 26 - May 1, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Nos. 54,100-54,199, May 1-31, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Nos. 54,200-54,299, June 3 - July 8, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Nos. 54,300-54,399, July 8 - August 30, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Nos. 54,400-54,499, September 4-26, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Nos. 54,500-54,599, September 27 - October 11, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Nos. 54,600-54,699, October 11-30, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Nos. 54,700-54,799, October 30 - November 16, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Nos. 54,800-54,899, November 16 - December 10, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Nos. 54,900-54,999, December 10, 1929 - January 4, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Nos. 55,000-55,099, January 4-28, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Nos. 55,100-55,199, January 29 - March 4, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Nos. 55,200-55,299, March 4 - April 9, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Nos. 55,300-55,399, April 10 - May 28, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Nos. 55,400-55,499, May 28 - July 10, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Nos. 55,500-55,599, July 10 - September 23, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Nos. 55,600-55,699, September 23 - October 30, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Nos. 55,700-55,799, October 30 - December 13, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Nos. 55,800-55,899, December 13, 1930 - January 21, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Nos. 55,900-55,999, January 21 - March 18, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Nos. 56,000-56,099, March 18 - May 20, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Nos. 56,100-56,199, May 20 - August 7, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Nos. 56,200-56,238; 56,329-56,399, August 10 - October 2, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Nos. 56,400-56,499, October 2 - December 5, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Nos. 56,500-56,599, December 5, 1931 - January 23, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Nos. 56,600-56,699, January 25 - March 26, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 35)
      - Nos. 56,700-56,799, March 29 - May 12, 1932; June 9 - August 10, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Nos. 56,800-56,899, December 10, 1932 - April 22, 1933; August 31 - September 5, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Nos. 56,900-56,999, April 25 - June 7, 1933; September 5 - November 14, 1933 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Nos. 57,000-57,045, November 14, 1933 - January 3, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A17,400-A17,499, April 11 - May 11, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A17,500-A17,599, May 12 - June 13, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A17,600-A17,699, June 14 - August 5, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A17,700-A17,799, August 7 - September 29, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A17,800-A17,899, September 29 - November 18, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A17,900-A17,999, November 4 - December 4, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A18,000-A18,099, December 4, 1902 - January 2, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A18,100-A18,199, January 2 - February 3, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A18,200-A18,299, February 5 - March 26, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A18,300-A18,399, March 26 - April 28, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A18,400-A18,499, April 28 - June 9, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A18,500-A18,599, June 9 - August 7, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A18,600-A18,699, August 10 - October 23, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A18,700-A18,799, October 23 - December 4, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A18,800-A18,899, December 4-24, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A18,900-A18,999, December 26, 1903 - February 2, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A19,000-A19,099, February 2 - March 17, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A19,100-A19,199, March 17 - April 26, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A19,200-A19,299, April 27 - June 8, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A19,300-A19,399, June 8 - August 22, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Nos. A19,400-A19,499, August 20 - October 24, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Nos. A19,500-A19,599, October 24 - December 1, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Nos. A19,600-A19,699, December 1-24, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Nos. A19,700-A19,799, December 24, 1904 - February 10, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Nos. A19,800-A19,899, February 10 - March 29, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 36)
      - Nos. A19,900-A19,999, March 24 - April 26, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A20,000-A20,099, April 26 - June 22, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A20,100-A20,199, June 23 - September 29, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A20,200-A20,299, September 29 - November 17, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A20,300-A20,399, November 20 - December 20, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A20,400-A20,499, December 20, 1905 - January 26, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A20,500-A20,599, January 26 - March 13, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A20,600-A20,699, March 13 - May 2, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A20,700-A20,799, May 3-25, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A20,800-A20,899, May 25 - July 7, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A20,900-A20,999, July 7 - September 25, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A21,000-A21,099, September 25 - November 23, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A21,100-A21,199, November 23 - December 26, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A21,200-A21,299, December 26, 1906 - February 19, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A21,300-A21,399, February 20 - April 25, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A21,400-A21,499, April 25 - July 2, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A21,500-A21,599, July 2 - August 26, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A21,600-A21,699, August 26 - November 9, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A21,700-A21,799, November 9 - December 9, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A21,800-A21,899, December 9, 1907 - January 10, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A21,900-A21,999, January 11 - March 23, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A22,000-A22,099, March 24 - May 22, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A22,100-A22,199, May 25 - July 22, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 37)
      - Nos. A22,200-A22,299, July 22 - October 19, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A22,300-A22,399, October 20 - December 1, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A22,400-A22,499, December 1-29, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A22,500-A22,599, December 30, 1908 - February 10, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A22,600-A22,699, February 10 - March 19, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A22,700-A22,799, March 22 - May 15, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A22,800-A22,899, May 18 - July 19, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A22,900-A22,999, July 22, 1909 - January 29, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A23,000-A23,099, February 1 - October 6, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A23,100-A23,199, October 6 - November 21, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A23,200-A23,299, November 21 - December 21, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A23,300-A23,399, December 21, 1910 - February 6, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A23,400-A23,499, February 6 - March 27, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A23,500-A23,599, March 27 - May 24, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A23,600-A23,699, May 24 - August 3, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A23,700-A23,799, August 3 - October 17, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A23,800-A23,899, October 18 - December 9, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A23,900-A23,999, December 11, 1911 - January 17, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A24,000-A24,099, January 17 - February 24, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A24,100-A24,199, February 24 - April 22, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A24,200-A24,299, April 23 - June 5, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A24,300-A24,399, June 5 - September 9, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A24,400-A24,499, September 10 - October 25, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A24,500-A24,599, October 26 - December 20, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Nos. A24,600-A24,699, December 13, 1912 - January 28, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 38)
      - Nos. A24,700-A24,799, January 28 - April 8, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A24,800-A24,899, April 10 - June 7, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A24,900-A24,999, June 9 - September 15, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A25,000-A25,099, September 18 - November 13, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A25,100-A25,199, November 13 - December 18, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A25,200-A25,299, December 18, 1913 - January 26, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A25,300-A25,399, January 26 - March 21, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A25,400-A25,499, March 23 - May 19, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A25,500-A25,599, May 21 - August 7, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A25,600-A25,699, August 8 - November 13, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A25,700-A25,799, November 13, 1914 - January 1, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A25,800-A25,899, January 1 - February 13, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A25,900-A25,999, February 15 - May 4, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A26,000-A26,099, May 4 - June 30, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A26,100-A26,199, June 30 - October 11, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A26,200-A26,299, October 11 - December 10, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A26,300-A26,399, December 10, 1915 - January 19, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A26,400-A26,499, January 19 - February 29, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A26,500-A26,599, March 1 - April 6, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A26,600-A26,699, April 6 - May 13, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A26,700-A26,799, May 15 - July 6, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A26,800-A26,899, July 6 - October 11, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A26,900-A26,998, October 11 - November 15, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A27,000-A27,099, November 15 - December 28, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 39)
      - Nos. A27,100-A27,198, December 28, 1916 - February 15, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A27,200-A27,299, February 17 - March 31, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A27,300-A27,399, March 31 - May 15, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A27,400-A27,499, May 16 - July 9, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A27,500-A27,599, July 9 - October 13, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A27,600-A27,699, October 13 - December 7, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A27,700-A27,799, December 10, 1917 - February 15, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A27,800-A27,899, February 19 - May 15, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A27,900-A27,999, May 17 - August 13, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A28,000-A28,099, August 13 - November 15, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A28,100-A28,199, November 16, 1918 - January 11, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A28,200-A28,299, January 11 - March 11, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A28,300-A28,399, March 12 - May 12, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A28,400-A28,499, May 13 - July 22, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A28,501-A28,599, July 24 - October 3, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A28,600-A28,699, October 4 - November 15, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A28,700-A28,799, November 15 - December 19, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A28,800-A28,899, December 20, 1919 - February 27, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A28,900-A28,999, February 27 - April 22, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A29,000-A29,099, April 22 - June 22, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A29,100-A29,199, June 22 - October 5, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A29,200-A29,299, October 5 - November 16, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A29,300-A29,399, November 16 - December 24, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A29,400-A29,499, December 27, 1920 - February 3, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Nos. A29,500-A29,599, February 3 - May 5, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Nos. A29,600-A29,699, May 6 - August 11, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 40)
      - Nos. A29,700-A29,799, August 11 - November 1, 1921 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A29,800-A29,899, November 1 - December 21, 1921 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A29,900-A29,999, December 22, 1921 - March 4, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A30,000-A30,099, March 4 - April 28, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A30,100-A30,199, April 28 - July 21, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A30,200-A30,266, July 24 - October 21, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A30,367-A30,399, October 23 - November 15, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A30,400-A30,499, November 15, 1922 - January 19, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A30,500-A30,599, January 19 - April 6, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A30,600-A30,699, April 9 - June 6, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A30,700-A30,799, June 6 - October 6, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A30,800-A30,899, October 6 - December 28, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A30,900-A30,999, December 29, 1923 - April 10, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A31,000-A31,099, April 10 - October 24, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A31,100-A31,199, October 24, 1924 - March 28, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A31,200-A31,299, April 4 - September 16, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A31,300-A31,399, September 18, 1925 - March 9, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A31,400-A31,499, March 10 - June 25, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A31,500-A31,599, June 29 - October 13, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A31,600-A31,699, October 13 - November 30, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A31,700-A31,799, November 30, 1926 - March 1, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A31,800-A31,898, March 1 - May 4, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A31,900-A31,999, May 6 - July 18, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A32,000-A32,099, July 20 - November 11, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Nos. A32,100-A32,199, November 11 - December 30, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Nos. A32,200-A32,299, December 30, 1927 - March 6, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Nos. A32,300-A32,399, March 6 - May 18, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Nos. A32,400-A32,499, May 18 - July 31, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 41)
      - Nos. A32,500-A32,599, September 4 - November 22, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A32,600-A32,699, November 22, 1928 - January 9, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A32,700-A32,799, January 9 - March 23, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A32,800-A32,899, March 28 - July 2, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A32,900-A32,999, July 2 - October 25, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A33,000-A33,099, October 26 - December 7, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A33,100-A33,199, December 7, 1929 - January 18, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A33,200-A33,299, January 20 - March 17, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A33,300-A33,399, March 17 - May 9, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A33,400-A33,499, May 12 - September 18, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A33,500-A33,599, September 18 - November 26, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A33,600-A33,699, November 28, 1930 - February 2, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A33,700-A33,799, February 2 - April 13, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A33,800-A33,899, April 13 - October 6, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A33,900-A33,999, October 7, 1931 - January 27, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A34,000-A34,099, January 29 - August 25, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Nos. A34,100-A34,199, August 25 - November 19, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Nos. A34,200-A34,299, November 22, 1932 - January 26, 1933 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Nos. A34,300-A34,399, January 30 - September 19, 1933 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Nos. A34,400-A34,499, September 19, 1933 - January 15, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Nos. A34,500-A34,599, January 15 - April 28, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Nos. A34,600-A34,699, May 3 - September 10, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Nos. A34,700-A34,799, September 10 - October 29, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Nos. A34,800-A34,899, October 30, 1934 - January 14, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Nos. A34,900-A34,999, January 14 - April 18, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Nos. A35,000-A35,099, April 22 - August 16, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 42)
      - Nos. A36,000-A36,099, August 19 - November 16, 1935 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Nos. A36,100-A36,199, November 16, 1935 - January 16, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Nos. A36,200-A36,299, January 17 - April 28, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Nos. A36,300-A36,399, April 28 - September 11, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Nos. A36,400-A36,499, September 11 - December 3, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Nos. A36,500-A36,599, December 3, 1936 - February 15, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Nos. A36,600-A36,699, February 9 - May 21, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Nos. A36,700-A36,799, May 21 - October 4, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Nos. A36,800-A36,899, October 4 - December 14, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Nos. A36,900-A36,999, December 14, 1937 - May 12, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Nos. A37,000-A37,099, May 12 - October 15, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Nos. A37,100-A37,199, October 15, 1938 - January 26, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Nos. A37,200-A37,299, January 26 - July 11, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Nos. A37,300-A37,399, September 5, 1939 - March 5, 1941; February 9 - March 3, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Nos. A37,400-A37,499, March 4 - May 7, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Nos. A37,500-A37,590, May 7 - July 8, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Nos. B4,200-B4,299, February 24 - December 8, 1902 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Nos. B4,300-B4,399, December 11, 1902 - December 17, 1903 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Nos. B4,400-B4,499, December 18, 1903 - February 1, 1905 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Nos. B4,500-B4,599, February 4 - December 6, 1905 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Nos. B4,600-B4,699, December 6, 1905 - October 3, 1906 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Nos. B4,700-B4,799, October 8, 1906 - November 9, 1907 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Nos. B4,800-B4,899, November 13, 1907 - March 22, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 23)